Guide to the School of Architecture, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1996-2013; Accession 2014-A-049
  - Course syllabi
    - 635b Exploring Glass, 2006 Spring (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 636a Sustainable Design, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 637a Issues in Environment and Design, 2000 Fall (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 638a Simulation and High Performance Green Design, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 638b Lighting, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 639a/639b Philosophy of Technology, 2000 Fall-2006 Spring (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 640b Architecture as Building, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 648b System Integration, 2000-2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 650a Critical Systems, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 655a Architectural Practice and Management, 2003-2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 657b Issues on Contemporary Practice, 2003 Spring-2007 Spring (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 661a 3D Form and Materials, 1999 Fall-2001 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 661b Materials and Morphology, 2006-2007 Spring (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 665a Material Formation in Design, 2004 Fall-2006 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 667b Craft, Materials and Computer-Aided Artistry, 2005 Spring-2007 Spring (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 668b Critical Architectural Systems, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - 670b Materials and Information-Advanced Metal Casting, 2004 Spring (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - 674a Architectural Product Design, 2000-2006 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - 676b Elaboration: Re-Materialization of Architecture, 2000 Spring (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - 678b Materials and Meaning, 2000 Spring-2007 Spring (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - 679b Digital Construction, 2003 Spring-2004 Spring (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - 680a Idea and Material-Jeanne Gang, 2005 Fall (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 680b Architecture as Building, 2004 Spring (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - 681b Furniture Design and Fabrication, 2000 Spring-2006 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - 682a Aluminum Design and Production, 2001 Spring-2006 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - 684b Fabrication-Smart Materials, 2000, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - 685a Architectural Practice and Management, 1998 Fall-2000 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - 686b Advanced Topics in Project Management, 2000 Spring (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 687b Topics in Practice Beyond Design, 2002 Spring (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - 688b Ornament and Technology, 2006 Spring-2007 Spring (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - 689b Component Prototyping in Architecture, 2005 Spring (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 695b Building plus Site, 2007 Spring (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 701a Modern Architecture, 2000-2006 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 703a Contemporary Architectural Theory, 2000 Fall-2007 Spring (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 704a Case Studies in Architectural Theory, 2003 Fall-2006 Fall (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 714a Methods and Research Colloquium, 2003 Fall-2006 Fall (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 717a Issues in Architecture and Urbanism, 2006 Fall (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 733b Lateral Strategies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 747b Japanese Modern Architecture, 2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 748b Gross Domestic Product, 2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 749b Berlin 1890-1920, 2004 Spring (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 750b Architectural Multiplications, 2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 751b Ornament Theory and Design, 2000 Fall-2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 752b Contemporary Architectural Discourse Colloquium, 2004 Spring-2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 753b Performance Criticism-Reyner Banham, 2004 Spring (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 757a The Construction of Exactitude-Classicism and Modernism, 2005 Fall-2006 Fall (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 759a Architectonics of Formalism (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 760a Critical Architecture, 2006 Fall-2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 760b Post War Architecture, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 761b Film Architecture, 2003 Spring (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 762b Modern American Architecture, 2000 Spring-2001 Spring (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 762b Form, 2004 Spring (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 763b Analysis of Architectural Form, 1999 Fall (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 764b Furness and Richardson, 1998-1999 Spring (Box 2, Folder 69A)
    - 765a History of Landscape Architecture, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 766b Introduction to British Landscape History, 2006 Spring-2007 Spring (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 767b Alvar Aalto, 2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 768a Writing on Architecture, 2006 Fall (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 771b History/Theory on Digital Technology, 2003 Spring-2004 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 772a James Stirling and the "Critical Turn", 2006 Fall (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 772b Architecture and Technique, 1999 Spring-2003 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 773a World's Fairs, 1999 Fall (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 775b Modern Space and Domesticity, 1999 Fall-2001 Spring (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 776a Opulence and Excess: The Architecture of Techno-Romanticism, 2006 Fall (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 776a Eero Saarinen, 2004 Fall-2005 Fall (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 777b Kahn in Context, 2004-2007 Spring (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 778b Architecture and (Un)Making of the Nation, 2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 778b Paris: Architecture and Urban Culture from St. Louis to Mitterand, 2000 Spring (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 780a/780b Architectural Form, 2006 Fall-2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - 783b Making Sense: Architecture, Technology and the Body, 2006 Spring (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - 784b Twenty-First Century Infrastructure (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - 784b The Post Industrial Factory, 2002 Spring (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - 784b Islamic Architecture, 2001 Spring (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - 785a Tropical Architecture, 1999 Fall (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - 785a Architecture and Revolution: Charles Moore, Postmodern Criticism and Political Activism at Yale in the 1960s, 2000 Fall (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 786a Mies van der Rohe and International Modernism, 2001 Fall (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 786b Beyond the Diagram: End Game Strategies for the Late Style, 2007 Spring (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - 787 Soane and Schinkel proposal, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 787a Millenium House, 2000 Fall (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - 788b Photography, Vision, Architecture, 2002 Spring (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - 790b Modern Architecture and Urbanism and Latin America, 2003 Spring (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 791a Rome Summer Drawing Program, 2000-2006 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 801a Introduction to Visual Studies: Formal Analysis, 2001 Fall-2006 Fall (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 802a Geometry, Drawing, and Visual Inquiry/808b Freehand Drawing (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - 803a Drawing and Architectural Forum, 2000 Fall-2006 Fall (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - 804b Drawing Projects, 2006 Spring (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - 811b Classical Drawing, 2006 Spring (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - 813a/813b Photography for Architects, Fall 2000-2006 Spring (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - 814b Advanced Photography for Architects (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - 827b Representation and Optics, 2002 Spring-2004 Spring (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - 828b Atmosphere and Effects, 2005 Spring-2006 Spring (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 836a Digital Space, 2003 Fall (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 851b/852b Intermediate Survey of Digital Media and Advanced Digital Media, 2006 Spring-2006 Summer (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - 860b Web and Interactive Media, 2001 Spring-2007 Spring (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - 862b Digital Video Synthesis, 2000 Spring (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 863b Digital Modeling: Maya, 2001 Fall-2002 Spring (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - 866a/866b Modeling, Animation, and Fabrication-3D Modeling, 2000 Fall-2006 Fall (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 868a Surface, 2004 Fall (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - 869a Form, Shape and the Emergence of Exoticism, 2005 Fall (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - 870a Eero Saarinen: Digital Modeling and Animation, 2005 Fall (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 871b Architecture After Stability, 2007 Spring (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - 872a Model Based Design, 2007 Fall (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 881a Evolutionary Design and Digital Fabrication, 2005 Fall (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - 887a Computer Aided Mapping, 2003 Fall (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - 902b Introduction to Urban Design: The Problem of the Modern City, 1999 Spring-2007 Spring (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - 903a Introduction to Planning and Management, 2000 Fall-2006 Fall (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - 905b Intermediate Planning and Development, 2000 Spring-2007 Spring (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - 911a The Public Realm, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 912a American Cultural Landscapes, 1999-2005 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 914b Built Environments and the Politics of Place, 2005 Spring-2006 Spring (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - 921a Studies in Historic Preservation, 2001 Fall (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - 922a Gender, Territory, and Space, 2000 Fall (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 925a The American Suburb, 2000 Fall-2005 Spring (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - 926a Globalization Space, 2006 Fall (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - 935a Case Studies in Development, 1999 Fall-2001 Fall (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - 941b Urban Research and Representation, 2007 Spring (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - 951b Architecture, Landscape and Art, Undated (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - 952b The Experience of Site, 2001 Spring (Box 3, Folder 132A)
    - 953b Architecture and Landscape, 2003 Spring (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - History courses taught by other schools and departments open to Architecture students, 2000 Fall-2006 Fall (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Event memorabilia, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 135)
- Records, 2004-2009; Accession 2016-A-040
  - Student evaluations and grades list, 2004 Fall (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Evaluation notes, 2004 Spring (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Course evaluations list, 2004 Fall (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Grades and evaluations-including web based grading, 2005 Spring (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Memos to outside faculty, 2005 Spring (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Grades and evaluations, 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Course evaluations-Spring 2007
    - ARCH 502 Architectural Design
    - ARCH 504 Architectural Design
      - D. Gans (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - ARCH 507 Digital Workshop for 506b-S. Farricielli (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Architectural Design Studio
      - ARCH 512-G. Lynn (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - ARCH 514-D. Porphyrios (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - ARCH 516-Z. Hadid (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - ARCH 518-A. Rahimi (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - ARCH 520-T. Beeby (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - ARCH 522-D. Berke (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - ARCH 524-D. Balmori (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - ARCH 526-K. Easterling (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - ARCH 602 Strucutres II-J. Axley (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - ARCH 640 Architecture as Building-T. Beeby (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - ARCH 648 Systems Integration
    - ARCH 657 Issues in Contemporary Practice-P. Bernstein (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - ARCH 661 Materials Morphology-J. Griggs (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - ARCH 667 Craft, Materials, Composite Aid and Artistry-K. Rotheroe (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - ARCH 678 Materials and Meaning-D. Berke (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - ARCH 684 Smart Materials-M. Addington (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - ARCH 688 Ornament Technology-B. Pell (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - ARCH 689 Component Prototyping in Architecture-J. Griggs (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - ARCH 695 Sites Buildings-S.Harris (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - ARCH 703 Contemporary Architectural Theory-A. Lourie (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - ARCH 747 Modern Japanese Architecture-H. Ota (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - ARCH 751 Ornament Theory Design-K. Bloomer (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - ARCH 759 Fragment and the Absolute-E. Petit (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - ARCH 761 Film Architecture-D. Neumann (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - ARCH 766 History of British Landscape-B. Fuermann (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - ARCH 777 Kahn in Context-C. Wiseman (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - ARCH 779 Design Disease: New Typologie-H. Sample (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - ARCH 781 Exit Utopia-D. Neumann (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - ARCH 786 Diagrammatic Analysis-P. Eisenman (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - ARCH 811 Classical Drawing-P. Pajares (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - ARCH 851 Intermediate Survey: Digital Media-J. Eberhart (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - ARCH 860 Web Design for Architects-J. Eberhart (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - ARCH 871 Architecture After Stability-M. Gage (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - ARCH 902 Introduction to Urban Design-K. Britton (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - ARCH 941 Urban Research Representation-E. Rubin (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Summer Drawing Course, 2007 Summer (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Summer Design Course, 2007 Summer (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Summer History/Theory Course, 2007 Summer (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Spring Class List (verified), 2007 Spring (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Course Evaluation List, 2007 Spring (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Course Evaluations-Spring 2009
    - ARCH 502 Architectural Design
    - ARCH 504 Architectural Design
    - Architectural Design Studio
      - ARCH 512
        - B. Buck (Box 1, Folder 76)
      - ARCH 514
        - D. Poryphiros (Box 1, Folder 77)
      - ARCH 516
      - ARCH 518
      - ARCH 520-W. Sharples (Box 1, Folder 83)
      - ARCH 522-T. Beeby (Box 1, Folder 84)
      - ARCH 524-K. Krumwiede (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - ARCH 602 Structures II-A. Gilbert (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - ARCH 618 Strcutres Facades: Tall Buildings-K. Moon (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - ARCH 640 Architecture as Buildings-T. Beeby (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - ARCH 648D System Integration Disc Sect
    - ARCH 661 Materials Morphology-J. Griggs (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - ARCH 667 Craft, Materials, Comparative Aid Artistry-K. Rotheroe (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - ARCH 681 Furniture Design Fabrication-P. de Bretteville (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - ARCH 682 Aluminum Casting Design-S. Parker (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - ARCH 688 Ornament Technology-B. Pell (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - ARCH 695 Sites Buildings-S. Harris (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - ARCH 703 Contemporary Architectural Theory-A. Harrison (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - ARCH 723 Independent Research (MED)-E. Pelkonen (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - ARCH 745 Extended Site: How the Cookie… (L. Fior) (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - ARCH 749 Case Studies in Architectural Criticism-C. Wiseman (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Couse Evaluations-Fall 2008
    - ARCH 501 Architectural Design
      - B. Buck (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - ARCH 503 Architectural Design
      - A. Benner (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - ARCH 509 Post Professional Studio
    - ARCH 511 Advanced Design Studio
    - ARCH 513 Advanced Design Studio
      - D. Schwarz (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - D. Cooke (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - ARCH 515 Advanced Design Studio
      - D. Balmori (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - ARCH 517 Advanced Design Studio
    - ARCH 519 Advanced Design Studio
    - ARCH 521 Advanced Design Studio
    - ARCH 601 Structures I-K. Moon (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - ARCH 625 Liquid Threshold
      - A. Chadwick (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - ARCH 633 Environmental Design-M. Addington (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - ARCH 636 Sustainable Design-M. Darling (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - ARCH 655 Architectural Practice-P. Bernstein (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - ARCH 665 Materials Formation in Design-K. Rotheroe (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - ARCH 674 Architectural Prodcut Design Innovation
    - ARCH 693 Studies in Light Materials-M. Addington (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - ARCH 701 Modern Architecture
      - D. Sherer (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - ARCH 704 Case Studies in Architectural Theory-A. Harrison (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - ARCH 714 Architectural Research Theories-M. Deamer (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - ARCH 717 Issues in Architecture Urbanism-A. Koetter (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - ARCH 746 Modernism Environmentalism-D. Barber (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - ARCH 747 Modern Japanese Architecture-H. Ota (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - ARCH 757 Construction of Exactitude-K. Britton (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - ARCH 760 Critical Architecture-M. Gooden (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - ARCH 765 History of Landscape Architecture-B. Fuermann (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - ARCH 768 Writing on Architecture-C. Wiseman (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - ARCH 771 Launch: Architect Entrepreneur-K. Easterling (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ARCH 780 Architectural Form-E. Mitchell (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ARCH 782 The Autobiographical House-K. Forster (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - ARCH 801 Introduction to Visual Studies-P. Eisenman (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - ARCH 802 Geometry, Drawing Visual…(P. Pajares) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - ARCH 803 Drawing Architectural Form-S. Gruzdys (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - ARCH 853 Computation Analysis-J. Eberhart (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - ARCH 882 Voluminous Surface Geometry-B. Buck (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - ARCH 903 Introduction to Planning Development-A. Garvin (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - ARCH 912 American Cultural Landscapes-D. Hayden (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - ARCH 926 Globalization Space-K. Easterling (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Course Evaluations-Summer 2008
    - History/Theory Course Evaluations (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Drawing Course Evaluations (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Digital Media Course Evaluations (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Design Course Evaluations (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Director of Undergraduate Studies, records, 1998-2010; Accession 2017-A-074
  Restricted until January 1, 2076
  - Arch 003b: Making an American Architecture-Turner Brooks, 2009 Spring (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arch 150a: Introduction to Architecture-Alexander Purves, 2001-2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arch 341b: Twelve Urban Landscape-Keller Easterling, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arch 152b: Introduction to Spatial Language-Kent Bloomer, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arch 154b: Drawing Architecture-Sophia Gruzdys, 2001-2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arch 161b: Introduction to Structure-Jim Axley, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Arch 162b: Materials for Architecture-Susan Farricielli, 2001-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arch 163b: Energy, Technology and Buildings-Michelle Addington, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arch 249a: The Analytic Model-Emmanuel Petit and Ariane Lourie, 2001-2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arch 250a: Methods and Forms in Architecture I: Deborah Gans and Amy Lelyveld, 2001-2008 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Arch 251b: Methods and Forms II: Sophia Gruzdys and Dean Sakomoto, 2002-2010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arch 342b: Eero Saarinen and His Times, Curriculum Development-Eeva-Liisa Pelkonen, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arch 344a: Urban Life and Landscape, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arch 350b: Suburbs and the Culture of Sprawl-Dolores Hayden, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arch 315a/AmSt 381a-Dolores Hayden, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CSBK 371: Envisioning Cities Methods of Representation-Joyce Hsiang, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Arch 381a: Mapping Space-Bimal Mandis, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arch 385a: New Haven and the American City-Alan Plattus, Douglas Rae and Elihu Rubin, 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Arch 431b/796b: Architecutre, Religion and Modernization-Karla Britton, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Arch 450a: Senior Fall Studio-Turner Brooks and Adam Hopfner (Design Seniors), 2001-2008 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Arch 461a/Hums 342b: Saarinen and Roche-Architecture, Power and Politics, 1948-1984-Eeva-Liisa Pelkonen, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Arch 490a: Senior Research Colloquim-Karla Britton (Senior Essay Preparation), 2001-2009 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Arch 495a: Senior Research Colloquim-Karla Britton (Senior Essay Preparation), 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Arch 491b: Senior Essay Projects-Victoria Casaco, Eeva-Liisa Pelkonen, Dolores Hayden, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Arch 494b: Advanded Senior Studio-Steven Harris and Tom Zook (Design Seniors), 1999-2009 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Arch 902b: Introduction to Urban Design-Karla Britton and Elihu Rubin, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Undergraduate Course Syllabi, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Records, 2005-2010; Accession 2018-A-001
  Restricted until January 1, 2086
  - Class list, 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Course Evaluations
    - Easterling, Keller: Arch 773-Lateral Strategies, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Wiseman, Carter: Arch 777-Kahn in Context, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Newmann, Deitrich: Arch 781-Exit Utopia, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Sanders, Joel: Arch 783-Making Sense of Space, Technology and Body, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Pelkonen, Eeva-Liisa: Arch 785-Kevin Roche Seminar, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Eisenman, Peter: Arch 786-Diagrammatic Analysis, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Deamer, Margaret: Arch 788-Architecture Post 9/11, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Marcantonio, Dino: Arch 811-Classical Drawing, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 8A)
    - Gage, Mark Foster:Arch 865-Design Reconaissance, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Harwell, Andrei S.: Arch 902-Civic Art, Intro to Urban Design, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Plattus, Alan J.: Arch 902-Civic Art, Intro to Urban Design, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Rubin, Elihu: Arch 902-Civic Art, Intro to Urban Design, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Garvin, Alexander: Arch 905-Intermediate Planing and Development, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Hayden, Dolores: Arch 914: Built Environments of Place, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Hayden, Dolores: Arch 925-Suburbs and Places of Sprawl, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Rubin, Elihu: Arch 941-Urban Research and Representation, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Arch 1011-Architectural Design Studio
    - Arch 1015-Visualization II: Form and Representation, 2009 Fall
    - Eisenman, Peter: Arch 1018-Formal Analysis, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Arch 1021-Architectural Design
    - Koetter, Alfred: Arch 1061-Post Pro Architectural Design Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Mitchell, Edward: Arch 1061-Post Pro Architectural Design Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Eberhart, John: Arch 1062-Computational Analysis Fabrication, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Buck, Brennan: Arch 1101-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Couture, Lisa Ann: Arch 1101-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Knight, George: Arch 1102-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Krier, Leon: Arch 1102-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Pasquarelli, Gregg: Arch 1103-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Price, Brian: Arch 1103-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Eisenman, Peter: Arch 1104-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Wang, Michael: Arch 1104-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Behnisch, Stefan: Arch 1105-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Eberhart, John: Arch 1105-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Bunge, Eric: Arch 1106-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Hoang, Mimi: Arch 1106-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Harwell, Andrei: Arch 1107-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Plattus, Alan J.: Arch 1107-Advanced Studio, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Agran, Victor: Arch 1211-Drawing and Architectural Form, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Bulman, Luke: Arch 1213-Books and Architecture, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Mitchell, Edward: Arch 1214-Architectural Form, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Buck, Brennan: Arch 1220-Fabrication and Façade, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Newton, Timothy: Arch 1224-The Chair, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Rowley, Joshua: Arch 1224-The Chair, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Moon, Kyoung Sun: Arch 2011-Structures I, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Addington, Michelle: Arch 2021-Environmental Design, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Darling, Michele Naomi: Arch 2021-Environmental Design, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Apicella, John: Arch 2031-Architectural Practice and Management, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Bernstein, Phillip: Arch 2031-Architectural Practice and Management, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 58)